question_data = [
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The Pythagorean theorem states that the square of the hypotenuse is "
                 "equal to the product of the squares of the other two sides.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Coca-Cola&#039;s original colour was green.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "Furby was released in 1998.", "correct_answer": "True",
                                      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Overwatch,&quot; an allied McCree will say &quot;Step right "
                 "up&quot; upon using his ultimate ability Deadeye.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Theodore Roosevelt Jr. was the only General involved in the initial assault on D-Day.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The open source program Redis is a relational database server.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "The capital of the US State Ohio is the city of Chillicothe.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Vehicles", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The General Motors EV1 was the first street-legal production electric vehicle.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The State of Queensland, Australia voted NO to a referendum for daylight savings in 1992.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Norway has a larger land area than Sweden.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Klingons once had a period of Democracy in their history, they referred to "
                 "it as the &quot;Dark Times&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Resident Evil 4 was originally meant to be a Nintendo GameCube exclusive.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In Portal, the Companion Cube&#039;s ARE sentient.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;League of Legends&quot;, there exists four different types of Dragon.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "You can square root a negative number with an imaginary number &quot;i&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The movie &quot;Tron&quot; received an Oscar nomination for Best Visual Effects.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The Korean War ended in 1953 without any ceasefire.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Avatar: The Last Airbender&quot; and &quot;The Legend of Korra&quot;, "
                 "Lavabending is a specialized bending technique of Firebending.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The original ending of &quot;Little Shop Of Horrors&quot; has the plants taking over the world.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Resident Evil&quot;, only Chris has access to the grenade launcher.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
